Your hair's so pretty, Mukuro.
There! All done!
Well? I've sure gotten good at this.
--And over here is--
--Asahi!
Look who it is!
Oh, wow! What brings you here?
They're friends from my school.
What a surprise.
--Hello.
--Nice to meet'cha.
You can see our school!
It looks so tiny from here.
Think we can see anyone
with the telescope?
We can't locate Tohka and Origami?
Right. They're not within east Tengu.
And we can't use GPS
since they left their phones.
Have the other Spirits
had any luck searching?
Not thus far.
What do you think, Reine?
Why did Tohka and Origami
act odd suddenly?
Regardless of why,
it's evident that Tohka
has become an Inverse Spirit.
As far as Origami, I think a second
personality has come forward.
Yeah. This world's history was rewritten.
Inside Origami are two personalities:
The Origami of the previous world and
the Origami of the world that changed.
But when I try to think about it,
my thoughts get all jumbled.
Why is that happening?
And who was it that changed the world?
Does it all revolve around Shido Itsuka?
Kotori, I've located their Spirit waves.
Dispatch a camera!
Roger.
I'm also detecting Spirit waves
from the two people they're with.
Two people?
One boy and one girl.
Though, the boy's waves appear abnormal.
What the hell is going on?
Seriously. What the hell is going on?
They kicked us out quick,
not that I'm surprised.
The fight's not over yet.
Take us to the next battlefield.
U-Um... Let's see...
Oh! There! Tengu Tower!
That's...
Oh? The view seems different
when you're not flying.
There's a legend that couples
who kiss up here live happily ever after.
I think it's fitting
for your next "battle."
Mukuro? What's wrong?
I don't know, but being here
gives me a bad feeling.
A bad feeling?
Mukuro, have you been here before?
Are you okay, Mukuro?
Mm.
I wonder what's up with Mukuro?
Hey, Tohka. What exactly are you?
What's an Inverse?
Actually, what are Spirits?
I resent being called "Inverse."
After all, it's the original
form of Spirits.
Huh? Meaning?
When the Spirit of Origin made Sephirah,
they were what you call "Inverse."
They were "refined" to be
compatible with humans.
H-Hold up! The Spirit of Origin?
To be compatible with humans?!
What do you mean by that?
Don't be mistaken, human.
I didn't answer to appease you,
but because I felt like it.
So weak. Maybe I'll just
steal a kiss by force.
You bitch!
Mukuro!
You dare try to steal him from Muku?!
Steal the one Muku loves?!
You think I care, mongrel?!
Mukuro!
How dare you cut Muku's hair!
Mister says that he likes it!
Mukuro! Stop!
Michael. Siffleur.
Oh? Very well.
Fighting this way is more my style.
Two huge Spirit waves!
One is Category E: Inverse!
Seal... We've gotta seal 'em somehow.
But how? How have we
sealed Spirits up until now?
Stop it, you two!
Kotori, it's Tobiichi.
Origami? What's going on?
Who are those Spirits?
I'll explain later. Can you slow them down
using Fraxinus' territory?
To a certain extent...
I'll handle the rest!
A-Are you nuts? Who are you anyway?
I know a way to stop them.
Can you trust me and help out?
Deploy Territory and Yggdrafolium!
Let's minimize collateral damage.
Why is it? Why do I feel like
we've done this countless times?
Soon, Fraxinus will hinder
their movements.
But I can't face both of them at once.
Origami, can you help?
Of course. If I let you go alone,
I'd get yelled at by the other me.
ID: Origami Tobiichi. Deploy Brunhild.
Falling for me, Itsuka?
Let's go, Origami!
Mm, Itsuka!
Raphael!
Cretin!
What?
Michael! Lataib!
Michael! Helles!
You can deconstruct Spirit armor
with that key?
I see. That's your play, huh?
I'll kill you! I'll kill everyone
who tries to steal him from Muku!
Wait, you two!
Please, calm down!
Getting in my way?!
Then I hope you're ready to entertain me!
Itsuka, stop Mukuro!
Kill! Kill! Kill all who try to steal him!
Muku hates being alone!
Mukuro!
Mister...
Please, stop this!
I don't want Tohka to be gone
or the others to forget me!
Everyone's a precious friend of mine!
--How...?
--Eh?
How can you say something like that?
Don't you love Muku?
Is Muku's love not enough for you?!
I hate being alone!
I won't let anyone take you!
Mukuro... What makes you say that?
There they are!
Tohka! Origami!
Why are they fighting?!
Eek! That's trouble!
Them, too?
Everyone wants to steal him
away from Muku! Unforgivable!
Michael! Segva!
Mukuro! What are you doing?!
Using Segva on the planet.
Eventually, it will stop spinning.
Then, none can interfere.
You and Muku can
stay in space together forever.
But first, I've gotta defeat her!
Mukuro!
--Guys!
--Huh? What?
You're that guy...!
Please, help me out! Mukuro--
the Spirit used her key on the planet!
At this rate, it'll stop spinning!
I need your power--the power of Spirits!
Okay. Fine by me.
Y-Yoshino? Shouldn't we think about it?
He doesn't seem like a bad person.
Also, I don't know how to explain it,
but I feel like I should help him.
Sure, why not? He asked nicely, after all.
Agreement. I don't know why,
but I feel like we've done this before.
Well, if you say so...
Why not? This sorta thing pumps me up!
Guys!
So, what should we do?
Well...
Guys, it's me. I'm communicating
through Territory.
--Kotori!
Like he said, Spirit power
has encroached the ground.
We'll plunge Yggdrafolium into six areas.
Use those as focal points
to send your Spirit power.
For a time, we'll be able
to stop the spread.
Can we trust you to handle this,
Shido Itsuka?
Yeah. Leave it to me.
Where will you go?
To the girl who needs my hand.
Tohka, please! Let's stop fighting!
You brought the fight to me!
I'm just making the most of it!
Metatron!
This time, I'll hit her body, not armor.
Even you won't survive
Michael's molecular destruction!
Michael! Helles!
Don't, Mukuro!
Here. This is for you.
With this, your hopes will come true.
Explain yourself!
You did this, didn't you?!
Nobody knew who I was at school today!
Not even my friends or the teacher!
What are you?! A freak?! A monster?!
Mukuro, you're...!
Gabriel! Haniel!
Mu... kuro...
No, Mister! I... I wasn't
trying to kill you!
No! Don't leave Muku all alone again!
Inversion?!
Don't! Stop, Mukuro!
Mukuro! Mukuro! Come back!
Mukuro, you're me! I was alone, too!
I learned the warmth of family when
the Itsuka's took me in, but...
I was always afraid that
I'd be abandoned--
that the people I loved
would move on and abandon me.
I was always terrified to think
my happiness might suddenly disappear.
Mukuro, you're scared, right?
So scared that it hurts.
Just like I was.
But listen, Mukuro.
There's nothing to worry about.
You're connected, no matter how
far away you are. That's what family is.
The Itsukas--my dad, mom,
and Kotori taught me that.
But I... I don't have...
I'll be your family!
So, you don't have to worry anymore.
I'll never forget you, no matter what.
No matter what happens,
I'll never hate you.
No, that's not enough.
You have to promise, too.
A one-sided love won't work.
After all, we're family.
Mister, I...
Mukuro...
Hmph. What a sad sight.
Tohka...
Itsuka!
Itsuka?
Don't interfere! Only I can
make Tohka normal again!
You turned that fighter into a baby.
I've lost interest.
Don't make me...
Don't make Tohka sad.
T-Tohka!
Itsuka! Let's get you
to Fraxinus' infirmary!
I'm fine 'cuz I've got Spirit power.
But Tohka and Mukuro--!
Don't let your guard down, Mister.
Tohka was able to kiss you.
Eh?
It's okay, I don't mind.
No matter what you do,
Muku won't worry anymore.
After all, we're family!
Mukuro...
Though...
Some level of intimacy is expected!
'Cuz we're family!
Um...
Family is... what to you?
I used to look at stars
with my sister like this.
Before Muku was a Spirit.
Why didn't I see it?
Why did Muku worry when Sis, Mommy,
and Daddy loved me so much?
It's natural. Nobody wants to be alone.
No one wants to lose
the place they belong.
Mister... You're the same as Muku.
Maybe that's why Muku
feels at ease around you.
You think I should cut my hair?
Huh?
Muku might wanna change things up.
You sure, Mukuro?
You'll cut it for Muku, won't you?
Other than family,
no one touches Muku's hair.
Yeah, you've got it.
Hurry or we'll be late!
If Origami stopped trying to climb
into Shido's coat, we wouldn't be!
My bad. I couldn't subdue
my animal instincts.
Morning!
How do you do, Shido? Long time no see.
Kurumi!
Starting today, I've returned to school.
I hope we can get along.
"Episode 08:
'Key and Sword.'"
The worst Spirit has returned.
Her goal? To take Shido's life
and Spirit power.
Next time:
"Nightmare's Seduction."
What awaits at the end
of this fierce battle?!
"Episode 09: 'Nightmare's Seduction.'"